Guide to the Records of the Office of the Chancellor/Executive Vice President (Borowitz) RG.6.0.7
New York University Archives
- Series XI: Schools and Departments
  - Arts and Science (WSUC), 1975 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Arts and Science (WSUC), Search for Dean, May 1973-Sep 1973 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Arts and Science (WSUC), Merger, Aug 1972-Dec 1973 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Divisions (FAS), Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Dec 1975-Apr 1977 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Divisions (FAS), Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Oct 1974-Nov 1975 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Divisions (FAS), Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Sep 1973-Jul 1974 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Divisions(FAS), Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Dec 1970-Jun 1973 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Divisions (FAS), Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Budget & Financial Matters, May 1971-Oct 1975 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Divisions (FAS), Institute of Fine Arts, Apr 1972-Jul 1976 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Divisions (FAS), Institute of Fine Arts, Budget and Financial Matters, Jul 1972-Jul 1976 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Divisions (FAS), Institute of Fine Arts, Budget and Financial Matters, 1972-1976 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Divisions (FAS), Goethe House (Deutsches Haus), Sep 1975-Feb 1977 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Divisions (FAS), Ibero-American Language and Area Center (IALAC), Sep 1971-Apr 1976 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Anthropology, Dec 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224999 8
  - Divisions, Departments(FAS), Anthropology, Jun 1974-Jul 1975 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Anthropology, May 1971-May 1974 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Applied Science, Jun 1976-Feb 1977 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Applied Science, Sep 1975-May 1976 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Applied Sciences, Jan 1975-Jul 1975 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Applied Sciences, Oct 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Applied Sciences, Jun 1973-Aug 1974 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Divisions, Departments(FAS), Biology, Nov 1973-May 1977 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Divisions, Departments(FAS), Biology, May 1971-Jul 1973 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Divisions, Departments(FAS), Chemistry, Oct 1971-Aug 1976 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Divisions, Departments(FAS), Chemistry, Levich Correspondence, Nov 1973-Sep 1976 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Classics, May 1971-1976 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Comparative Literature, Mar 1973-Dec 1975 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Economics, Sep 1974-Aug 1976 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Economics, Oct 1973-Aug 1974 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Economics, Sep 1971-Jun 1973 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), English, Oct 1970-Feb 1977 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), French and Italian, Jul 1971-Sep 1976 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225000 4
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Geology, May 1972-Jan 1977 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), German, Jan 1969, Jan 1975-May 1976 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), History, Jan 1970-Mar 1976 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Journalism, Feb 1973-Jan 1976 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Misc, Jun 1972-Mar 1976 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Music, Jun 1973-Mar 1977 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Near Eastern Language and Literature and Kevorkian Center for Near East Studies, Apr 1971-Feb 1977 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Philosophy, May 1973-Dec 1976 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Physics, Sep 1974-Oct 1976 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Physics, Nov 1973-Apr 1974 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Physics, Feb 1972-Jul 1973 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Politics, Mar 1971-Nov 1976 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Psychology, Nov 1971-Mar 1976 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Slavic Languages and Literature, Jun 1973-Nov 1976 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Divisions, Departments(FAS), Sociology, Jun 1972-Mar 1976 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Divisions, Departments (FAS), Spanish and Portuguese, Apr 1972-Jun 1976 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Business School (BPA), Feb 1975-Apr 1976 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Business Schools (BPA), Sep 1973-Jul 1974 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Business Schools (BPA), Jan 1972-Jul 1973 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Business Schools (BPA), Retail Management, Institute of, Oct 1972-Feb 1974 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Business Schools (GBA), Jul 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Business Schools (GBA), Mar 1976-May 1976 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225001 2
  - Business Schools (GBA), Sep 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Business Schools (GBA), Jan 1975-Jun 1975 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Business School (GBA), Sep 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Business Schools (GBA), Sep 1973-Aug 1974 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Business Schools (GBA), Jun 1973-Aug 1973 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Business Schools (GBA), May 1971-May 1973 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Business Schools, Budget & Financial Matters, Sep 1975-Jun 1976 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Business Schools, Budget & Financial Matters, Jun 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Business Schools, Budget & Financial Matters, Nov 1974-May 1975 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Business Schools, Budget & Financial Matters, Sep 1973-Jul 1974 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Business Schools, Budget& Financial Matters, Oct 1972-Mar 1973 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Business Schools, Budget & Financial Matters, Jan 1971-Aug 1972 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Business Schools, Merger of BPA and GBA, Mar 1971-Oct 1973 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Business Schools, Programs, Feb 1975-Mar 1976 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Business Schools, Programs, Mar 1972-Nov 1974 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Business Schools, "Schools of Business" Weekly Digest, Aug 1973 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Apr 1976-Mar 1977 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225002 0
  - Continuing Education, School of, Dec 1975-Mar 1976 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Sep 1975-Nov 1975 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Continuing Education, School of, May 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Sep 1974-Apr 1975 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Apr 1974-Aug 1974 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Jan 1973-Mar 1974 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Continuing Education, School of, May 1971-Dec 1972 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Budget & Financial Matters, Oct 1975-Dec 1976 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Budget & Financial Matters, Jan 1972-Aug 1975 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Dean, Jun 1972-Feb 1976 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Faculty Meeting Minutes, Sep 1974-Nov 1976 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Misc, Feb 1974-Mar 1976 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Real Estate Institute, Nov 1973-May 1975 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Sawhill Reorganization Proposal, Jan 1976-Jun 1976 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Sawhill Reorganization Proposal, Nov 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Sawhill Reorganization Proposal, Sep 1975-Nov 1975 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Search for a Dean, Feb 1976-Sep 1976 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Continuing Education, School of, Search for a Dean: Candidates, undated (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Dentistry, College of, Sep 1976-Jan 1977 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225003 8
  - Dentistry, College of, Sep 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Dentistry, College of, Sep 1974-Aug 1975 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Dentistry, College of, Apr 1970-Aug 1974 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Dentistry, College of, Matters, Accreditation, Oct 1964, Feb 1973-May 1975 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Dentistry, College of, Survey Manual for the Evaluation of the Dental Education Program, Oct 1973 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Dentistry, College of, Budget & Financial Matters, Jul 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Dentistry, College of, Budget & Financial Matters, Sep 1974-May 1975 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Dentistry, College of, Budget & Financial Matters, Mar 1972-Aug 1974 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Dentistry, College of, Complaints, Feb 1974-Jul 1974 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Dentistry, College of, Construction, Sep 1975-Nov 1976 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Dentistry, College of, Construction, May 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Dentistry, College of, Construction, Jan 1973-Apr 1975 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Dentistry, College of, Construction, May 1972-Oct 1973 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225004 6
  - Dentistry, College of, Construction, Income and Expense Statements, Jul 1971-Jun 1976 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Dentistry, College of, Construction: Proposal Material (1), undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Dentistry, College of, Construction: Proposal Material (2), undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Dentistry, College of, Construction: Proposal Material, Jun 1972 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Dentistry, College of, Dean, Sep 1972-Feb 1977 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Dentistry, College of, Dean's Memoranda, Jan 1976-Sep 1976 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Dentistry, School of, Materials for Chancellor for May 6, 1975 Meeting with State Education Department, May 1975 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Dentistry, College of, Misc, Jun 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Dentistry, College of, Misc, May 1973-Apr 1975 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Dentistry, College of, Misc, Jun 1972-Apr 1973 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Dentistry, College of, Search for a Dean, Dec 1973-Apr 1975 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Dentistry, College of, Search for a Dean, Curricula Vitae, Mar 1974-May 1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Dentistry, College of, State Options Regarding Dental Schools, Jun 1974-Jul 1975 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Dentistry, Medicine, Schools of Programs (AB-DDS and AB-MD), Dec 1973-Dec 1976 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Education, School of, Sep 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225005 3
  - Education, School of, Jun 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Education, School of, Jan 1976-May 1976 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Education, School of, Sep 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Education, School of, Jan 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Education, School of, Sep 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Education, School of, May 1974-Aug 1974 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Education, School of, Jan 1974-Apr 1974 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Education, School of, Feb 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Education, School of, Budget & Financial Matters, May 1970-Dec 1972 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Education, School of, Budget & Financial Matters, Sep 1971-Nov 1975 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Education, School of, Dean, Sep 1973-May 1976 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225006 1
  - Education, School of, Dean, Nov 1971-Aug 1973 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Education, School of, Departmental Productivity Studies, AY 1974-1975, 1975-1976, 1974-1976 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Education, School of, Faculty Meeting Minutes, Agendas, Apr 1974-Mar 1977 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Education, School of, Faculty-Ed Council Meeting Minutes, Dec 1971-Apr 1977 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Education, School of, Financial Report, 1973-1974 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Education, School of, Financial Report, 1972-1973 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Education, School of, Financial Report, 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Education, School of, Misc, Sep 1974-Jun 1976 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Education, School of, Misc, Sep 1973-Jul 1974 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Education, School of, Misc, Jan 1971-Jul 1973 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Education, School of, Nurse Education Division, Oct 1973-Jan 1977 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225007 9
  - Education, School of, Nursing, Proposal for School of, Feb 1972 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Gallatin Division (University Without Walls), Jan 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Gallatin Division (University Without Walls), Sep 1973-Dec 1975 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Gallatin Division (University Without Walls), Apr 1973-Jul 1973 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin Division (University Without Walls), Mar 1971-Oct 1972 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin Division (University Without Walls), Associate in Arts Audio Program, Jul 1973-Nov 1974 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Gallatin Division (University Without Walls), Associate in Arts Audio Program, Jun 1972-Jun 1973 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Gallatin Division (University Without Walls), Budgets and Financial Matters, Oct 1972-Sep 1973 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Gallatin Division, Search for a Director, Apr 1976-Jul 1976 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Gallatin Division, Search for a Director, Candidates, undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Gallatin Division (University Without Walls), Union for Experimenting Colleges and Universities Publications, Feb 1970-Apr 1976 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Law, School of, Feb 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Law, School of, Oct 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Law, School of, May 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Law, School of, Jan 1975-Apr 1975 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Law, School of, Sep 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Law, School of, May 1973-Aug 1974 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225008 7
  - Law, School of, Jan 1971-Apr 1973 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Law, School of, Budget & Financial Matters, Mar 1973-Jun 1976 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Law, School of, Dean, Apr 1973-May 1975 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Law, School of, Faculty Meeting Minutes, Mar 1974-Feb 1977 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Law, School of, Law Center Foundation, Sep 1974-Mar 1976 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Law, School of, Law Center Foundation, Nov 1972-Aug 1974 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Law, School of, Law Center Foundation: A New Memorandum of Understanding - NYU and Law Center Foundation, Jul 1976-Oct 1976 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Law, School of, Law Center Foundation: A New Memorandum of Understanding - NYU and Law Center Foundation, Apr 1974-Jan 1975 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Law, School of, Foundation, Budgets and Financial Matters, Jan 1971-Apr 1975 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Law, School of, Search for a Dean, Sep 1974-May 1975 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Medical Center, Midtown Hospital Merger, Mar 1973-Aug 1974 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Medical Center, Newsletters, Misc, Oct 1972-Mar 1973 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Medical Center, Urban Health Affairs, Nov 1972-Jun 1975 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Sep 1975-Feb 1977 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Sep 1974-Aug 1975 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Sep 1973-Jul 1974 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Sep 1972-Jul 1973 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225009 5
  - Medicine, Schools of, May 1969-Aug 1972 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Affirmative Action, Nov 1973-Nov 1975 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Affirmative Action, Nov 1971-Oct 1972 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Budget & Financial Matters, Feb 1975-Nov 1975 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Budget & Financial Matters, Aug 1972-Jul 1974 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Budget & Financial Matters: Indirect Costs, Jan 1971-Jun 1974 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Budget & Financial Matters: Financial Reports Prepared by Manufacturers Hanover, Mar 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Budget & Financial Matters: Financial Reports Prepared by Manufacturers Hanover, Jan 1973-Dec 1975 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Budget & Financial Matters: Financial Reports Prepared by Manufacturers Hanover, Jul 1972-Oct 1973 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Budget & Financial Matters: Misc Reports, Sep 1970-Apr 1973 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Budget & Financial Matters: Monthly Report of Sponsored Research and Training, Mar 1972-Jan 1976 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Faculty Council Meeting Minutes, Jun 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Department Chairmen, Council of, Meeting Minutes, Sep 1974-Nov 1976 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Meeting Minutes, Jun 1975-Jan 1976 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Medicine, Schools of, Programs, Jun 1973-Apr 1976 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Public Administration, Graduate School of, Sep 1975-Dec 1976 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225010 3
  - Public Administration, Graduate School of, Oct 1974-Jul 1975 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Public Administration, Graduate School of, Mar 1971-Apr 1974 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Public Administration, Graduate School of, Budgets and Financial Matters, Jan 1971-Dec 1975 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Public Administration, Graduate Schools of, Dean, Jun 1972-Feb 1977 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Public Administration, Graduate School of, Faculty/Student Council Meeting Minutes, Sep 1974-Sep 1975 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Public Administration, Graduate School of, Institute of Labor Relations, Mar 1973-Apr 1974 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Social Work, School of, Oct 1975-Jan 1977 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Social Work, School of, Sep 1974-Jul 1975 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Social Work, School of, Sep 1972-Jul 1974 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Social Work, School of, Apr 1968-Jul 1972 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Social Work, School of, Accreditation Review, Jun 1973-Jul 1975 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Social Work, School of, Budget & Financial Matters, Feb 1971-Jul 1975 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Social Work, School of, Center for Studies in Income Maintenance Policy, Jan 1973-Jun 1975 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Social Work, School of, Campaign for School Survival, May 1972-Jun 1973 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Social Work, School of, Center for Studies in Income Maintenance Policy, Jun 1971-Dec 1972 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Social Work, School of, Dean, Apr 1973-Nov 1976 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Social Work, School of, Faculty Meeting Minutes, Agendas, undated (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Social Work, School of, Search for Dean, Feb 1970-Mar 1975 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225011 1
  - Arts, School of the, Sep 1973-Jan 1977 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Arts, School of the, Sep 1974-Aug 1975 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Arts, School of the, Oct 1973-Aug 1974 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Arts, School of the, Sep 1972-Jul 1973 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Arts, School of the, Sep 1971-Jun 1972 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Arts, School of the, Dec 1968-Aug 1971 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Arts, School of the, Jun 1965-May 1967 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Arts, School of the, Alternate Media Center, Oct 1974-Sep 1975 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Arts, School of the, Alternate Media Center, Sep 1973-Aug 1974 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Arts, School of the, Alternate Media Center, Sep 1972-Aug 1973 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Arts, School of the, Budget & Financial Matters, Jun 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Arts, School of the, Budget & Financial Matters, Jun 1972-May 1975 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Arts, School of the, Dean, Sep 1968-May 1976 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Arts, School of the, Faculty Meeting Minutes, Apr 1975, May 1975 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Divisions, Afro-American Affairs, Institute of, Sep 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Divisions, Afro-American Affairs, Institute of, Oct 1974-Aug 1976 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Divisions, Afro-American Affairs, Institute of, Oct 1968-Jul 1974 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225012 9
  - Divisions, Afro-American Affairs, Institute of, Budget & Financial Matters, Jan 1974-Mar 1977 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Divisions, Afro-American Affairs, Institute of, Clippings, Other Institutions, Dec 1969-Apr 1974 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Divisions, Brazilian Institute, Jul 1972-May 1973 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Counseling Services, Jan 1974 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - International Studies, Center for, Jan 1970-Oct 1975 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Series XII: Student Activities
  This series addresses matters concerned with students. It comprises 2.5 linear feet of material contained in 6 Hollister boxes. Categories included range from Admissions to Work Study, with the largest and possibly most interesting groupings dedicated to Admissions, Financial Aid, and the Office of Student Affairs. Box 76 and folders 1-5 of Box 77 consist of documents covering Admissions matters, some of which date from the late 1960's. Associated reports and statistical information in Box 77, folders 4-5 include yearly reports covering the period 1971-1976.
  Financial Aid files occupy box 78, folders 9-19 and Box 79, folders 1-5. Transactions concerned with the special undergraduate admissions program funded by NYSED at private institutions throughout the state under the title Higher Education Opportunities Program#(HEOP) appear in folders 11-16. NYU's was the largest program in the state. The University's own financial aid program, supported by internal budget allocations, was called the Martin Luther King Jr. Program. These records in this collection appear in Box 78, folders 18-19.
  Box 80, folders 10-17 contain the records of the Office of Student Affairs. The Office was headed by a director at the time these records commence, in 1972; that Director, Jane Maggin, was named Assistant Chancellor for Student Affairs and Housing two year later, 4/13/74, folder 12, as the initiatives and demands of that function grew. The period saw increasing needs to focus, for example, on questions of student life, 8/30/74, folder 11, and 5/16/74, folder 12, management of housing facilities, 9/9/74, 5/29/74 and 12/20/73, folder 12, feeding students, 3/19/73, folder 13, the use of drugs and other criminal activity by or directed toward students, 12/2/74, folder 11, 9/21/73, folder 12, as well as the emerging need to provide recreation facilities for students, Box 27, folder 9.
  - Divisions, Other University, 1972-1975 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Divisions, Special Programs, Cooperative Program with University of Warsaw, Mar 1972-May 1974 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Divisions, Sunrise Semester, Jun 1972-Aug 1976 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Divisions, Testing Center, Feb 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Divisions, Town Hall, Jan 1972-Mar 1977 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Divisions, Urban Center, Jan 1971-Feb 1972 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Divisions, Weekend College, Oct 1972-Oct 1975 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Divisions, Weekend College, Jun 1972-Aug 1972 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Admissions, Oct 1975-Jun 1976 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225013 7
  - Admissions, Sep 1974-Jun 1975 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Admissions, Sep 1972-May 1974 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Admissions, Sep 1969-Aug 1972 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Admissions, Empire State College, Mar 1973-Nov 1973 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Admissions, Empire State College, Mar 1971-Feb 1973 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Admissions, Press Coverage, Other Printed Materials, undated (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Admissions, Reports and Statistics, Jun 1976-Mar 1977 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Admissions, Reports and Statistics, Jan 1976-May 1976 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Admissions, Reports and Statistics, Jun 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Admissions, Reports and Statistics, Jan 1975-May 1975 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Admissions, Reports and Statistics, Jul 1973-Aug 1974 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04225014 5
  - Admissions, Reports and Statistics, Jan 1973-Jun 1973 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Admissions, Reports and Statistics, Feb 1971-Jul 1972 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Admissions, Yearly Reports, Sep 1975-Sep 1976 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Admissions, Yearly Reports, Sep 1971-Sep 1974 (Box 77, Folder 5)